dubaitrade.ae 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://www.dubaitrade.ae/privacy-policy)

Dubai Trade FZE and its affiliates (collectively referred to here as "Dubai Trade") are committed to protecting your privacy online. We appreciate that you do not want the personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here we explain how we collect information on or via the portal (www.dubaitrade.ae) (the "Portal"), what we do with that information and what controls you have in relation to it. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms and Conditions which govern all use of the Portal. 

**What information do we collect about you?**

In the course of your use of the Portal, you provide us with certain information, which may be broadly described as General Information and Personal Information. 

_General Information_ : We receive more general information from you as a result of your visits to, and use of, the Portal. This general information does not identify you personally, and can include information such as your IP address, the length of time you spend on the site, your browsing history, and other such 'General Information'. 

_Personal Information_ : We also receive more personal information about you, such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and various details about your company upon registration. Each time you use the Portal we will also ask you for your user name and password. 

We may store or access some information (commonly known as a " **cookie** ") on your computer when you access the Portal. This information facilitates your use of the Portal and helps us to provide you with the best level of service. For example, cookies ensure that you do not need to re-enter your details every time you visit the Portal and help us to show you advertisements which are relevant to your interests. 

You can erase or block cookies from your computer if you want to (your help screen or manual should tell you how to do this), but certain services available on the Portal may not work correctly if you set your browser not to accept cookies. 

**How is your information used?**

Dubai Trade collects your Personal Information and General Information to enable us, amongst other things, to provide our services on the Portal to you and to allow us to better understand our users and improve the layout and functionality of the Portal. In summary, your Personal Information and General Information is used to:

  * Open and manage your registration with the Portal
  * Identify you each time you visit the Portal (by checking your computer for our cookie)
  * Operate the Portal, and bill you for services purchased on the Portal
  * Track of your use of the Portal
  * Generate aggregate statistics about Portal visitors
  * Send you information you have requested through the Portal
  * Notify you about products and services that may interest you (see below)
  * Also, we may share your information with certain third parties as outlined below

**With whom is your information shared?**

Dubai Trade will pass parts of your information to third parties who assist in providing you with the services available on the Portal or in the payment for those services (such as banks and payment platform providers). Unless you tell us you do not want us to, Dubai Trade may disclose your Personal Information to business partners or sponsors to allow them to contact you by email about products and services that may interest you. Dubai Trade cannot be held responsible for the actions of those third parties to whom we disclose your Personal Information.

Dubai Trade may analyse and disclose aggregate statistics about visitors to the Portal, customers and sales in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

Dubai Trade may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Dubai Trade, the Portal or its visitors.

If Dubai Trade is sold to a third party, or Dubai Trade otherwise becomes subject to a merger, consolidation or acquisition, it would become necessary for us to transfer your Personal Information to a third party, and in such case Dubai Trade would require that the third party handles your Personal Information with no less care than taken by us.

**Links** The Portal contains links to other third party sites. Dubai Trade is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

**Security**

Dubai Trade places a great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our customers. We have implemented technology and policies to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access. Although we have appropriate systems in place, we and our providers cannot guarantee and will not be held responsible for any unauthorised access by third parties.

**Where is the information stored?**

Information which you submit via the Portal is held on a computer located in the emirate of Dubai in the United Arab Emirates.

**Your acceptance**

By using or registering on the Portal and therefore accepting the Terms and Conditions of which this Privacy Policy forms part, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Dubai Trade as set out above. If we change the Privacy Policy in any way, we will post these changes on this page and you should check this regularly.

Thank you for your cooperation. We hope you find the Portal helpful and convenient to use. Please e-mail us with any other concerns regarding the Privacy Policy or the contents of the Portal: [info@dubaitrade.ae](mailto:info@dubaitrade.ae)

These Terms were last updated in January 2012.
